<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Golang on </title>
    <link>/tags/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Golang on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CannaBlis</title>
      <link>/articles/cannablis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/cannablis/</guid>
      <description>CBD lifestyle brand Tribe Tokes kicks off its entry into beauty with a natural CBD eye cream from Kym B It’s Here! A CBD eye cream from a girl who knows cannabis. Tribe Tokes own director of operations, Kymberly “KymB” Byrnes, a cannabis advocate, influencer and all-around girl boss is behind a natural CBD line, Cannablis By KymB Beauty. With so much knowledge and passion for cannabis, Kim, a certified Pilates instructor &amp;amp; self-proclaimed “green juice junkie” vegetarian knew she had to explore good natural ingredients that would work well with CBD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CannaGather</title>
      <link>/articles/cannagather/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/cannagather/</guid>
      <description>CannaGather is the largest cannabis industry community in New York. Join us for a lecture style event with amazing speakers plus a great networking community. No cannabis consumption is allowed at our events, due to New York State law&amp;hellip;we hope this will change!
 Upcoming CannaGather Events
 Columbia, the future of Canna-Agriculture
December 11th, 2018 7:00pm– 9:00pm
Galvanize
303 Spring Street
New York, NY 10013
CannaGather is the largest cannabis industry community in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honeysuckle Magazine</title>
      <link>/articles/honeysuckle-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/honeysuckle-magazine/</guid>
      <description>HONEYSUCKLE is a print and digital magazine that emphasizes diverse voices, personal testimony, and visual impact. Each quarter, our print edition explores a topical issue through a range of perspectives. Our boots-on-the-ground reporting combines input from thoughtful observers, high-profile celebrities, and personal testimony. Our cross-generational audience is open, inclusive, and curious, united by their shared passion for knowledge and desire to dive deep into themes that are important.
In the most recent issue of Honeysuckle, our very own KymB has a published piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kym&#39;s Updates</title>
      <link>/articles/kym-s-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/kym-s-updates/</guid>
      <description>What an exciting time in the world of weed! As your official plug for news and events, I have been struggling to create a hub for all of the amazing opportunities in the cannabis community. After months of compiling and an amazing team - I launch Cannabis with KymB Online Platform. Here you can find all things cannabis specifically on the (B) East Coast.
It’s no secret that I LOVE cannabis in all shapes, sizes and forms #girlwhosmokes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NuggMD</title>
      <link>/articles/nuggmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/nuggmd/</guid>
      <description>About NuggMD NuggMD is the fastest, easiest, and most secure way to get your medical marijuana recommendation and card, granting you instant access to the California cannabis industry. We believe pioneering a new era in cannabis means brandishing new behaviors and attitudes, ones that expose misinformation and uncover truths. It&amp;rsquo;s our mission to reveal cannabis for what it really is by facilitating easier access to it and empowering consumers with reliable information, personalized support and attention, and a conviction that puts your needs at the highest level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PussyWeed</title>
      <link>/articles/flower-power-coffee-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/flower-power-coffee-copy/</guid>
      <description>PussyWeed™ is an apparel, accessories and media company aiming to de-stigmatize women in cannabis as well as advocate for the end to the war on drugs. It all began in the summer of 2016 as a group of friends who found empowerment in a space which freely allowed us to experience cannabis as wellness. Feeling distanced from media portrayals and real-life manifestations of cannabis culture, especially regarding femmes, we found that in our feminine setting we were able to ask any question, tell any story, and share &amp;amp; learn any information without fear or insecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tribe Tokes</title>
      <link>/articles/tribe-tokes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/tribe-tokes/</guid>
      <description>_ABOUT TRIBETOKES_ TribeTokes creates and distributes merchandise with an elevated aesthetic for the next generation cannabis consumer - who respects plant science, consumes mindfully and expects top quality products from trusted brands. We are dedicated to elevating the acceptance &amp;amp; aesthetics of the industry and celebrating its thriving community. MINDFUL, FIT AND LIT https://www.tribetokes.com/ Featured Product
 https://www.tribetokes.com/collections/home-page-collection-keybox-flip-battery/products/starter-vape-kit-set-adjustable-voltage-pen-battery-510-thread
WHY WE LOVE IT Wait no longer! Our classy and sophisticated all white vape pen is here, and ready to blow a customized cloud just for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>